(Penny:)-Maybe you'll have another chance--
-No.
(Sheldon:)I will never have another chance
to have gelato with Stan Lee...
(Sheldon:)...because opportunities
(Sheldon:)...come but once in a lifetime.
(Sheldon:)The moving finger writes
and, having writ, moves on.
(Penny:)Did he just somehow
give me the finger?
(Howard:)Not just the finger, the moving finger.
(Leonard:)Hey, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Oh, hey, Penny. Wow.
(Scene:)Hi.
(Leonard:)-What's going on?
-Nothing.
(Stuart:)I'm just getting ready to close up
and head out.
(Penny:)-Cool. Got any fun plans?
-Oh, yeah. Big night tonight.
(Stuart:)Gonna share a can of tuna
with the cat.
(Penny:)Oh, nice.
(Stuart:)Not even my cat. I just feed it.
Some nights, it doesn't even show up.